<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Week8Venues</string>
    <string name="cafe_du_monde">Cafe du Monde</string>
    <string name="la_colombe">La Colombe</string>
    <string name="stumptown">Stumptown</string>
    <string name="sightglass">Sightglass</string>
    <string name="blue_bottle">Blue Bottle</string>
    <string name="visit_website">Visit Website</string>

    <!-- Cafe du Monde -->
    <string name="cdm_addy">800 Decatur Street  New Orleans, LA 70116</string>
    <string name="cdm_phone">(504) 525-4544</string>
    <string name="cdm_hours">Open 24 Hours</string>
    <string name="cdm_html">http://www.cafedumonde.com/</string>
    <string name="cdm_history">The Original Cafe Du Monde Coffee Stand was established in 1862 in
        the New Orleans French Market. The Cafe is open 24 hours a day, seven days a week. It closes
        only on Christmas Day and on the day an occasional Hurricane passes too close to
        New Orleans.\n\nThe Original Cafe Du Monde is a traditional coffee shop. Its menu consists of
        dark roasted Coffee and Chicory, Beignets, White and Chocolate Milk, and fresh squeezed
        Orange Juice. The coffee is served Black or Au Lait.\n\nAu Lait means that it is mixed half
        and half with hot milk. Beignets are square French -style doughnuts, lavishly covered with
        powdered sugar. In 1988 Iced Coffee was introduced to the cafe. Soft drinks also made their
        debut that year.</string>

    <!-- La Colombe -->
    <string name="lac_addy">400 Lafayette St  New York, NY 10003</string>
    <string name="lac_phone">(212) 677-5834</string>
    <string name="lac_hours">Mon–Fri 7:30 AM–6:30 PM, Sat–Sun 8:30 AM–6:30 PM</string>
    <string name="lac_html">http://www.lacolombe.com/</string>
    <string name="lac_history">Todd Carmichael and JP Iberti founded La Colombe on a simple but
        profound premise: America Deserves Better Coffee. By sourcing and roasting with care, and
        borrowing on ancient and modern coffee traditions from around the world, the two have built
        a successful company and an elevated coffee experience for Americans. Through 20 years of
        hard work and innovation, the two have made sure that experience is shared in cafes and
        homes across the country.\n\nIn addition to supporting our coffee-producing communities,
        we seek to support, nurture, and enhance the local neighborhoods that are home to our cafes.
        From providing free coffee to a nearby homeless shelter to helping with the community garden
        across the street, we work hard to engage with our environment and create meaningful
        connections with our neighbors.\n\nHere at La Colombe, we are keenly aware of where our
        coffee comes from, how it was grown, and, most importantly, the needs of the people involved
        in the coffee’s journey from seed to cup. We care deeply about the wellbeing of
        coffee-growing communities, and we strive to implement the best business practices to
        increase that wellbeing.</string>

    <!-- Stumptown -->
    <string name="stm_addy">18 W 29th St  New York, NY 10001</string>
    <string name="stm_phone">(347) 414-7805</string>
    <string name="stm_hours">Mon–Fri 6:00 AM–8:00 PM, Sat–Sun 7:00 AM–8:00 PM</string>
    <string name="stm_html">http://www.stumptowncoffee.com/</string>
    <string name="stm_history">Coffee is about pleasure. It’s that moment when your hand is warmed
        by the mug, you raise it to your nose, inhale deeply and then take a sip. That sip is the
        culmination of years of work, three-thousand mile journeys, and passion. Here is how we
        make that sip perfect.\n\nStumptown Coffee Roasters is a coffee roaster and retailer based
        in Portland, Oregon, United States. The chain\'s flagship café and roastery opened in 1999.
        Three other cafes, a roastery and a tasting annex have since opened in Portland, as well
        as locations in Seattle, New York, Los Angeles, Chicago, and New Orleans.\n\nWe don’t buy
        in bulk on a trading floor. We buy directly from the people who are making the coffee.
        It’s not a transaction; it’s a partnership. If someone is growing the quality of coffee
        we’re interested in, then we will help them in any way we can. That means regular visits
        (even though that trip can take up to four days), implementing new techniques and equipment,
        and forming long-term partnerships.</string>

    <!-- Sightglass -->
    <string name="sgl_addy">270 7th St  San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="sgl_phone">(415) 861-1313</string>
    <string name="sgl_hours">Mon–Sat 7:00 AM–7:00 PM, Sun 8:00 AM–7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="sgl_html">http://www.sightglasscoffee.com/</string>
    <string name="sgl_history">Our company takes its name from the \'sightglass,\' the viewing
        window on our vintage PROBAT coffee roaster that exposes the complex and delicate process
        of roasting coffee. We believe that knowing the story behind your coffee—where it was
        grown, how it was processed, and who handled it along the way—is a powerful link from the
        cup to the wider world.\n\nIn 2009, we began with a small, rickety service-cart in San
        Francisco’s SoMa district. Equipped with a few Chemex pots and a leaky vintage 2-group
        espresso machine, we served coffee to the neighborhood just behind a roll-up garage door
        housed in a sturdy 1914 built warehouse. People came to visit us, and remarkably, even came
        back to taste more.\n\nTwo years and many coffees later, the entirety of this warehouse would
        become our production roastery, a dynamic and unconventional coffee bar, a community
        gathering space, and our company headquarters.</string>

    <!-- Blue Bottle -->
    <string name="bbl_addy">66 Mint Plaza  San Francisco, CA 94103</string>
    <string name="bbl_phone">(510) 653-3394</string>
    <string name="bbl_hours">Mon–Sun 7:00 AM–7:00 PM</string>
    <string name="bbl_html">http://bluebottlecoffee.com/</string>
    <string name="bbl_history">In the early 2000s, in Oakland, California, a slightly disaffected
        freelance musician and coffee lunatic, weary of the commercial coffee enterprise and stale,
        overly roasted beans, decided to open a roaster for people who were clamoring for the actual
        taste of fresh coffee.\n\nUsing a minuscule six-pound batch roaster, he made a historic vow:
        “I will only sell coffee less than 48 hours out of the roaster to my guests, so they may
        enjoy coffee at peak flavor. I will only use the finest, most delicious, and responsibly
        sourced beans.”\n\nNow, nearly 15 years later, and thanks to the enthusiastic support
        of many loyal guests, Blue Bottle Coffee has grown to a small network of cafes, an espresso
        cart, the occasional pop-up, and a small fleet of Loring roasters. We are still united by
        the simple purpose of getting great coffee to everyone who asks for it. We have gotten even
        more specific about freshness and peak flavor.\n\nImprobably and delightfully, there are
        hundreds of us now.</string>

</resources>
